{
    "subject": "resource/Liberty_Hall_(Barnstable,_Massachusetts)",
    "predicate": "property/locmapin",
    "object": "Massachusetts",
    "human_readable": "Liberty Hall in Barnstable, Massachusetts is located in Massachusetts.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9550145268440247,
            "question": "Is Liberty Hall in Massachusetts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7906515598297119,
            "question": "If you were visiting Barnstable, Massachusetts, what landmark could you find there?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.755438506603241,
            "question": "Where is Liberty Hall located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6423500776290894,
            "question": "In what state is Liberty Hall situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5845582485198975,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Liberty Hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4671151041984558,
            "question": "Which state is known for having Liberty Hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4552241861820221,
            "question": "What is the name of the state where Liberty Hall is found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4455014169216156,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the location of Liberty Hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3023146986961365,
            "question": "To which US state does Liberty Hall belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09916233271360397,
            "question": "Where is this historical building found?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Liberty Hall in Barnstable, Massachusetts is located in Massachusetts.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5956_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which US state does Liberty Hall belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5956_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about the location of Liberty Hall?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5956_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the state where Liberty Hall is found?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5956_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5956_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n**Triple:** Liberty Hall in Barnstable, Massachusetts is located in Massachusetts.\n\nAfter reviewing the context information, here's my answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that two documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5956/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5956/re-ranker-msmarco/27.txt) mention that Liberty Hall is located in Barnstable, Massachusetts, which is indeed a state in the United States. Therefore, it can be inferred that Liberty Hall is located in Massachusetts."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Liberty Hall is located in Marstons Mills, which is a village in the town of Barnstable, Massachusetts. Therefore, it can be concluded that Liberty Hall is indeed located in Massachusetts."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}